[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Goonies, Mouth denies Chunk access into the Walsh house unless he does what?", "correct_answer": "Shakes his fat belly", "incorrect_answers": ["Tells a story", "Says Mouth is the Master", "Does 1 push up"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The moment to serve the risotto has come.  Let it stand for three minutes so that flavours mix, then prepare the plates. To serve risotto properly, you should do what with the plates?", "correct_answer": "Preheat them", "incorrect_answers": ["Wet them", "Wipe them out", "Freeze them"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does australo mean?", "correct_answer": "South", "incorrect_answers": ["South Africa", "The Australian Outback", "Australia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "We get this word from the name of a French Ambassador to Portugal.", "correct_answer": "nicotine", "incorrect_answers": ["leotard", "zinnia", "tariff"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Dodgeball, Peter learned from Kate that Average Joes Gym was $50,000 in debt.  How do Peter and his friends first try to raise money to get out of this debt?", "correct_answer": "by having an all male car wash", "incorrect_answers": ["by selling magazine subscriptions", "by having Steve the Pirate rob a bank", "by having a bake sale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The diamond is chosen as the birthstone of this month.", "correct_answer": "April", "incorrect_answers": ["August", "March", "December"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which skeletal muscle extends the foot, and is used to stand on tiptoes?", "correct_answer": "Gastrocnemius", "incorrect_answers": ["Hamstrings", "Soleus", "Tibialis anterior"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which EU country or US state is not entirely situated on (an) island(s)?", "correct_answer": "Rhode Island", "incorrect_answers": ["UK", "Hawaii", "Cyprus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the man that had hiccups for nearly 69 years?", "correct_answer": "Charles Osborne", "incorrect_answers": ["Carl Rexfort", "John Hannah", "Rhett Milfrond"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor played Murphy Brown\u2019s son in the Murphy Brown sitcom.", "correct_answer": "Haley Joel Osmont", "incorrect_answers": ["Scott Bryce", "Jake Gyllendall", "Jay Thomas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is it true that in the movie Princess Protection Program Carter and Rosies high school is called Lake Monroe High School?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which countrys blue division helped Germany on the Eastern front during WWII?", "correct_answer": "Spain", "incorrect_answers": ["Turkey", "Italy", "Japan"]}]